<!DOCTYPE idea-plugin PUBLIC "Plugin/DTD" "http://plugins.intellij.net/plugin.dtd">
<idea-plugin url="http://www.jsrana.com/home/idea/quicknotes">
    <name>Quick Notes</name>
    <description><![CDATA[
    Quick Notes plugin provides ability to quickly save notes within IDEA. This plugin allows managing multiple notes.
    Please save your existing notes before upgrading (just in case).
    <br><br>For any bugs or suggestions, please leave a comment on the plugin page at
    <br><a href='http://plugins.intellij.net/plugin/?id=4456' target='_blank'>http://plugins.intellij.net/plugin/?id=4456</a>
    <p><b><u>Change Log</u></b>
    <p><b>Version 2.5</b>
    <ul>
    <li>The Note is no more locked if opened in multiple IDEA instances. Any changes to a Note gets reflected in other opened instances as well in real time.</li>
    <li>IDEA instances are now kept in sync when a Note is Added or Deleted or Renamed</li>
    </ul>
    <p><b>Version 2.4</b>
    <ul>
    <li>Bug fix for Line number alignment (thanks WarnerJan)</li>
    <li>Added popup menu to editor</li>
    </ul>
    <p><b>Version 2.3</b>
    <br>The data is now saved in a file under user's home directory under folder ".ideaquicknote"
    and if for some reason the saving of data fails then data is saved in the plugin's internal storage.
    QuickNotes is now also compatible with multiple IDEA instances. Please save your existing notes before
    upgrading to this version (just in case).
    <ul>
    <li>Data is now saved in user's home directory</li>
    <li>Shows line numbers with an ability to hide it</li>
    <li>Compatible with multiple IDEA instances</li>
    <li>Minor UI tweaks</li>
    </ul>
    ]]></description>
    <version>2.5</version>
    <change-notes>
        <![CDATA[
    <p><b>Version 2.5</b>
    <ul>
    <li>The Note is no more locked if opened in multiple IDEA instance. Any changes to a Note gets reflected in other opened instance as well in real time.</li>
    <li>IDEA instances are now kept in sync when a Note is Added or Deleted or Renamed</li>
    </ul>
    <p><b>Version 2.4</b>
    <ul>
    <li>Bug fix for Line number alignment (thanks WarnerJan)</li>
    <li>Added popup menu to editor</li>
    </ul>
    <b>Version 2.3</b>
    <br>The data is now saved in a file under user's home directory under folder ".ideaquicknote"
    and if for some reason the saving of data fails then data is saved in the plugin's internal storage.
    QuickNotes is now also compatible with multiple IDEA instances. Please save your existing notes before
    upgrading to this version (just in case).
    <ul>
    <li>Data is now saved in user's home directory</li>
    <li>Shows line numbers with an ability to hide it</li>
    <li>Compatible with multiple IDEA instances</li>
    <li>Minor UI tweaks</li>
    </ul>
    <p><b>Version 2.2</b>
    <br>This version includes some nice UI tweaks
    <ul>
    <li>Added ability to see list of all notes and select any one of them</li>
    <li>Changed text background as a notepad</li>
    </ul>
    <p><b>Version 2.1</b>
    <br>This version is a minor update to allow saving the notes to a file
    <ul>
    <li>New ability to save notes to a file</li>
    </ul>
    NOTE: If you are upgradig from v1.0, then please save your existing note first.
    <br>(thanks WarnerJan for pointing this out)
    <br>
    <p><b>Version 2.0</b>
    <br>This version is a major update to previous version with many new functionalities
    <ul>
    <li>New ability to add multiple notes</li>
    <li>New ability to delete a note</li>
    <li>New ability to rename the title of a note</li>
    <li>New ability to navigate multiple notes</li>
    <li>Now also shows the created date of a note</li>
    <li>Changed background color of notes to light yellow</li>
    </ul>
    ]]>
    </change-notes>
    <vendor email="jsrana@gmail.com" url="http://www.jsrana.com" logo="/resources/quicknotes32.png">Jitendra Rana
    </vendor>
    <idea-version since-build="7000"/>
    <application-components>
        <component>
            <implementation-class>com.jsrana.plugins.quicknotes.QuickNotes</implementation-class>
        </component>
    </application-components>
</idea-plugin>